Hello hello namaste friends so how is everyone
welcome to my channel Desh Mein Buniyaad and
Change Travel E Do today we are going to
talk about delivery and
subscribe my channel
if you like my video then like and
press the bell icon to get the next
notification
so let's begin
[Music]
Lut
Hello friends I am here so friends today I am
talking about the update of electric scooter I don't know suddenly the delivery has become faster since last two-three days
everyone has
started getting scooters as
they had said that everyone will get scooter before 28k
or so and there are some of my friends
who have not received the scooter yet whose
dispatch has not happened yet so all those people
messaged me and told me that their scooters have been
delivered I got a message on YouTube
I got a Facebook message so
this delivery process is
going very smoothly it has become faster since last three days
many people have received the delivery and there are
some of my friends who have
not received the delivery yet whose dispatch has not happened
so I will request Ola to arrange the
delivery of these people as soon as possible  Give me the scooter, give me the dual SIM
and I want to request that the customer
care support is not that good, please
look into this matter, the customer does not say anything,
nothing is clear to him, the
robot only says whatever it says, so there is
no customer support here, customer care means when we
call us, we should get a solution
but we do not get any solution, customer
care knew something or you do not know anything, so I
want to give another point that they are
asking for Aadhar card OTP verification,
many people were telling me by commenting,
I also talked to customer care,
what did customer care say, they are
asking for address verification at some places, delivery has been done many times,
which are in cities, but one such
scooter can be processed and delivered in three-four days
and the rest of the villages,
their process is getting delayed because they are facing
some problem in getting their logistics there
and they are facing some
problem in the RTO registration also.  This is
because they have given the contract to a third party.
Ola's Enron tattoo is getting
faster. It will take some time at night to
see the delivery but the delivery has started for the
untrained people and everyone has started getting the
juice and OTPs
and the registration process has
also started and some people
apply for their PIN subsidies from the government and they
also have a little problem. Some
people have Aadhaar card and
their PIN
subsidies are not getting applied. Due to this reason
also many people's scooters
are pending and many of my friends have done this
work by taking inspiration and have paid
2000 rupees but due to not taking it,
theirs is not getting delivered. I did it for
less money, there is not much difference,
only
2500, you will see the difference. If you
compare the price then come with Saver Mode but I would
say that you should take insurance
so that your scooter gets delivered quickly.
You are getting a third party insurance and one year insurance from Payas and you are getting full interest on them.
Here if you take it from the insurance
then you will get some smooth express
and if you take it from outside then
you need the receipt number and engine
number because for registration
and for taking the policy its jersey
number and engine number are required and here the oil does
not have enough support for the customer to provide
you the receipt number and engine number
and that is why your scooter is not getting delivered.
Till date I have received many messages
and on YouTube that I have not taken it so
what should I do, I spoke to the customer care,
you do one thing, call the customer and
tell them that my installation which was not taken,
give my details to the finance department and I have to take insurance from there, if you take the
license then
you will get the scooter as soon as possible,
why are you saying this because without
insurance they are not delivering the scooter to you,
many people have
applied for third party but when you update the invoice to them through email, there is
no response from them and so
understand here that if you do not take the insurance from me then it will
not be delivered to you, it will take
time or if you do not get the scooter as soon as possible  If you
want,
you can pay VAT below if you don't want unhealthy potatoes,
but why am I saying this
because you are not getting response from email,
customer care is not supportive,
not giving you any tips, as far as the
customer I spoke to, he said
give us the details, we will
give your details to the financial department, then they can
call and you can insure it, so
friends, this is the reason also because of insurance,
right now there is a lot of water crisis, the
ending is coming, it will be delivered to everyone by 125th,
some people who are
in villages may also get their master, then the
third match will start after March, their
payment will also start being taken, so friends,
my request was that you
think about the installation, those who have not believed,
what should you do, and in this, the
price dialogue ID value will be reduced,
our X1 Pro, in this you are getting ₹1.50 something,
you have developed with the state number
and if you take MS Word then unlimited, so our
premium will be less, so thinking this,
officer juice gets it, crazy button take
Care Bye-Bye